

Professional Profile

Certified in Information Technology and Cybersecurity by Google, with outstanding skills in IT Support, Python Automation, Cybersecurity, Project Management, Data Analysis, User Experience Design, and Digital Marketing. My diverse background reflects adaptability and proactivity, and my goal is to apply my newly acquired knowledge in challenging IT roles.

Contact



+34 611 48 84 27



gabri_82@hotmail.com



C/ Palestina 5, 10D, Malaga



linkedin.com/in/gabriel-lobato-309894288/

Skills

- Programming: Python, C/C++, R.
- Database: SQL, NoSQL.
- Cloud Computing: AWS, Google
 Cloud.
- Git y GitHub

GABRIEL LOBATO

Work Experience

Comdata

Malaga - Spain

• Bilingual Customer Service Operator for Mango

Job&Talent

Malaga - Spain 2020

• Amazon Procurement and Distribution Logistics

Star Multiservices

Houston - Estados Unidos 2014 - 2017

• Accounting Administrator

ASI Constructors Inc

Houston - Estados Unidos 2013 - 2014

• Construction Surveyor and Professional Diver

ETINCSAC

Lima - Peru 2013

Surveyor

Academia Tecnimar

Malaga - Spain 2013

Administrative clerk

Telepizza SA

Málaga - España 2009 - 2013

Store Manager

Freelance

International since 2014

 Graphic Design, Illustration, Motion Graphics, Multimedia Design, Video Editing, Special Effects, 3D Design, UI/UX Design

- Operating Systems Administration:
 Windows, Linux.
- Automation: Puppet, PowerShell, Bash.
- Project Management: Agile,
 SCRUM, Kanban, XP, Lean.
- Cybersecurity: Red Team | Blue Team, Information Security, Network Security: SIEM Tools (Splunk, Chronicle), CTF, NIST, ISO, GDPR, CISSP, CIA triad, IDS, CIS, SOCs, IDS, SOAR, Suricata, Packet Sniffers...
- IT Infrastructure: Hardware, Software, Networks.
- Infrastructure Management.
- Data Visualization: Tableau, Power
 BI, Google Looker Studio.
- Graphic & Multimedia Design:
 Adobe Master Collection, Adobe
 XD, UI/UX, Figma, Canva.
- Code debugging and troubleshooting techniques.

Soft Skills

- Adaptability
- Proactivity
- Effective Communication
- Troubleshooting
- Time Management
- Teamwork
- Negotiation
- Leadership
- Presentation Skills
- Organization
- Project Management
- Resilience

Education

University of Malaga

2002 - 2007

Bachelor's Degree in Industrial Design Engineering

IES La Rosaleda, Malaga

2010 - 2012

Higher Technician in Urban Development Projects and Topographic Operations

Certifications

The Bridge

2024

Cybersecurity Bootcamp

Oxford Home Study Center (OHSC)

2024

Diploma in Cybersecurity

Google

2023

- IT Support Professional Certificate
- IT Automation with Python Professional Certificate
- Cybersecurity Professional Certificate
- Data Analysis Professional Certificate
- Project Management Professional Certificate
- User Experience Design Professional Certificate
- Digital Marketing and E-Commerce Professional Certificate

IMFE Málaga

2023

PYTHON: Back-End Programming & Development Bases

FEMXA

2021

AWS Architect Professional Certificate

Languages

English C1

English C1 Certificate Mainfor School of Languages English C1 Certificate Official School of Languages of Malaga English Diploma: Business Management

French B2

French B1 Certificate Official School of Languages of Malaga French Diploma: Business Management

German A2

German Diploma: Customer Service